{
    "questions":[
        {
            "key":1,
            "question": "What did Kevin buy for himself when he got himself for Secret Santa?",
            "answers": ["M&Ms", "A foot bath", "A trip to Sea World", "A balloon"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "key":2,
            "question": "What's in the thermos that Michael offers Pam during morning deliveries for the Michael Scott Paper Company?",
            "answers": ["Black coffee", "Sugar and cream", "Coffee and sugar", "Milk and sugar"],
            "correct": 4
        },
        {
            "key":3,
            "question": "What's the brand of the women's suit Michael accidentally buys?",
            "answers": ["MISSterious", "Ann Taylor", "Karen Millen", "Dorothy Perkins"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "key":4,
            "question": "Who started the fire?",
            "answers": ["Ryan", "Toby", "Pam", "Oscar"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "key":5,
            "question": "Jim sends an urgent message back to Dwight posing as Dwight from the future, warning him that something in the office was poisoned. What was it?",
            "answers": ["Water", "Salt", "Muffins", "Coffee"],
            "correct": 4
        },
        {
            "key":6,
            "question": "Which of these is not a name of Angela's cat?",
            "answers": ["Crinklepuss", "Pawlick Baggins", "Muffin", "Sprinkles"],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "key":7,
            "question": "How much did Michael's plasma TV, the one that Jan destroyed, cost?",
            "answers": ["100$", "200$", "300$", "400$"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "key":8,
            "question": "Who is Michael Scarn married to?",
            "answers": ["Angelina Jolie", "Sandra Bullock", "Hilary Swank", "Catherina Zeta-Jones"],
            "correct": 4
        },
        {
            "key":9,
            "question": "Who fakes their own death in the series finale?",
            "answers": ["Creed", "Ryan", "Dwight", "Toby"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "key":10,
            "question": "Who gave Michael the Worldâ€™s Best Boss mug?",
            "answers": ["Dwight", "He bought it for himself", "Pam", "Everybody from the office together"],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}